
exports.questionAsJSON =  [
    {
        "id":1,
        "question": "Capital of India ?",
        "answers": ["Delhi","Goa","UP"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question": "The language spoken by the people by Pakistan is ?",
        "answers": ["Hindi","Palauan","Sindhi","Nauruan"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question": "The World Largest desert is ?",
        "answers": ["Thar","Kalahari","Sahara","Sonoran"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question": "Country that has the highest in Barley Production ?",
        "answers": ["China","India","Russia","France"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question": "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is ?",
        "answers": ["Zinc","Silver","Copper","Aluminium"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question": "The Central Rice Research Station is situated in ?",
        "answers": ["Chennai","Cuttack","Bangalore","Quilon"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question": "Mount Everest is located in ?",
        "answers": ["India","Nepal","Tibet","China"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question": "Which soil is suitable for agriculture ?",
        "answers": [" Red soil","Sand","Black soil","Peaty soil"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question": "Black soils are best suited for the cultivation of ?",
        "answers": ["Cotton","Rice","Sugarcane","Cereals"]
            
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question": "The device used for measuring altitudes is ?",
        "answers": ["altimeter","ammeter","audiometer","galvanometer"]
            
    }
]
/*
AnswerSheet = [
    {
        "id":1,
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "answer":1
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "answer":1
    }
]

exports.GetAnswerSheet = function(qustionId){
    AnswerSheet.find(data=>data.id === questionId)
}
*/